爸爸走了
Dad's gone now.
他希望我们继续他的事业
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
怎么样 我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
What do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
（忆往昔）
鲍比 那把刀
Bobby, that knife.
什么样的刀能杀恶魔
What kind of blade can kill a demon?
昨天的话 我会说没有这种东西
Yesterday, I'd have said there was no such thing.
打不死恶魔的 如果那是你的目标
Won't stop a demon if that's what you think.
你是谁
Who are you?
有点疼呢
This smarts a little.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你到底要不要我帮你修枪
Do you want me to help you out with that gun or not?
你一发现这个露比是个恶魔
The second you find out this Ruby chick is a demon,
就该去拿圣水 不是跟她闲聊
you go for the holy water. You don't chat.
我们没闲聊 迪恩
No one was chatting, Dean.
是吗 那你怎么没把她送回地狱
Yeah? Then why didn't you send her ass back to hell?
她说她能帮你
She told me she could help you, okay?
她知道你的弱点是我
She knows what your weakness is. It's me.
你觉得我弟弟是不是有毛病
You think something's wrong with my brother?
不
No.
恶魔都撒谎
Demons lie.
据我所知 迪恩还是要下地狱
Last I checked, Dean's still going to hell.
凡事急不得 萨姆
Everything in its own time, Sam.
你得做一些
You're gonna have to do things.
有违你温柔天性的事
that go against that gentle nature of yours.
好的一面是
On the bright side…
我也会陪伴你
I'll be there with you.
你肩膀上的小堕落天使
That little fallen angel on your shoulder.
（如今）
那个派对简直太烂了
That was just a terrible, terrible party.
但倒是有个特别美丽的女人在场
But there was this one really beautiful woman there.
你该跟她回家的
You should've gone home with her.
我是跟她回家了
I did.
我需要点时间
I need a few minutes.
好
All right.
冰箱里有瓶89年的红酒
There's a bottle of '89 in the fridge.
很好
Good.
天啊
God.
怎么…
What the…?
保罗
Paul?
怎么了
What is it?
我的牙
It's my teeth…
珍妮特
Janet!
救我
Help me!
[邪恶力量 第3季第9集]
她是那么害怕
She was so scared.
我帮不了她 我完全无力阻止
I couldn't help, I couldn't do anything to stop it.
我跟警方谈过了
And I've talked to the police.
跟法医也谈过了
and I've talked to the medical examiner.
他们都无法解释
And no one can explain it.
所以他们才联系了我们 达顿先生
Well, that's why they put the call in to us, Mr. Dutton.
但疾控中心 那是疾病控制吧
But the CDC, that's disease control, right?
你们怎么想 是病毒吗
What do you think, it's some kinda virus?
我们不能排除任何可能
We're not ruling out anything yet.
达顿先生 珍妮特有敌人吗
Mr. Dutton, did Janet have any enemies?
什么
I'm sorry?
会有人有理由想伤害她吗
Anyone that might have a reason to hurt her?
等等 什么
Wait. What…?
你什么意思 有人给她下毒了吗
What are you saying? That somebody poisoned her?
我就是说 我们得考虑到一切
Just saying we have to cover every base here.
但是什么样的毒呢
But, I mean, what kind of poison?
这会是什么人做的吗
You think a person could've done this?
会有人想这么做吗
Would anyone want to?
什么 不会
What? No. No.
没有人会…
There's no one that could have…
达顿先生
Mr. Dutton?
每个人都爱珍妮特
Everyone loved Janet.
好吧
Okay.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我们应该不缺什么了
I think we've got everything we need.
我们不打扰你了
We'll get out of your way now.
你觉不觉得那人有所隐瞒
That dude seemed a little evasive to you?
我不知道 我在水池下面
I don't know. I was under a sink.
找这个呢
pulling this out.
巫术袋
Hex bag.
- 恶心 - 嗯
- Gross. - Yeah.
有鸟骨 兔牙
There are bird bones, rabbit's teeth.
这块布应该是从珍妮特·达顿的衣服上剪下来的
This cloth is probably cut from something Janet Dutton owned.
那么是女巫了
So we're thinking witch.
对 而且不是新世纪巫士占卜什么的
Yeah, and not some New Age Wiccan water dowser either.
是古老的黑魔法 迪恩
This is Old World black magic, Dean.
满脸疖子那种
I mean, warts and all.
我讨厌女巫
I hate witches.
总是把自己的体液吐的到处都是
Always spewing their bodily fluids everywhere.
- 差不多吧 - 真瘆人
- Pretty much. - It's creepy.
而且极其不卫生
You know, it's downright unsanitary.
是啊
Yeah. Well,
绝对有人仇视珍妮特·达顿
someone definitely had it out for Janet Dutton.
嗯 那人溜了进去 放了巫术袋
Yeah, someone who snuck into that house and planted the bag.
怎么回事
So what are we thinking,
是住在树林里 满脸皱纹的布莱尔女巫吗
we're looking for some craggy old Blair Bitch in the woods?
不 可能是任何人
No. Could be anyone.
邻居 同事 男人 女人
Neighbor, coworker, man, woman.
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
他们跟其他人一样 也是人
They're human like everyone else.
好啊 那我们怎么找到那人
Great. How we gonna find them?
这不是随机案件
This wasn't random.
珍妮特·达顿生活中有一个跟她有仇的人
Someone in Janet Dutton's life had an ugly ax to grind.
- 我们找到动机 - 就能找到杀人犯
- We find the motive… - We find the murderer.
嗯
Yeah.
阿曼达
Amanda.
Amanda!
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
抱歉 我心事太多了
Sorry. I've got like a thousand things on my mind.
你还好吗 亲爱的
Are you okay, sweetie?
你昨晚没来参加读书俱乐部
You didn't come to book club last night.
嗯 抱歉 我本想打电话的 但我太忙了
Yeah. Sorry. I was gonna call. I just… I got busy. You know?
但我没事 真的
But I'm fine. Really,
真没事 谢谢
I am. Thanks.
这顿晚餐是给你准备的 保罗·亚瑟·达顿
This dinner was cooked for you, Paul Arthur Dutton.
现在你要吃下它
Now you're going to eat it.
查看车里
Check the car.
萨姆
Sam?
找到了
Got it!
来 来
Come on. Come on.
你没事吧
You okay?
我这是遇上什么事了
What the hell is happening to me?
有人杀了你妻子
Someone murdered your wife.
现在还想杀你 就是这种事
And now they're trying to kill you. That's what's happening.
那不可能 不会的…
That's impossible. There's no way…
保罗 要不是我们跟踪了你
Paul, if we hadn't been following you,
你这会儿就死了
you'd be a doornail right now.
谁想要你死
Now, who wants you dead?
快想想看
Come on. Think.
有个女人
There's a woman…
好 有个女人
Okay, a woman?
- 好 - 我出轨了 那是个错误
- Okay. - An affair. A mistake.
她心态不平衡 还勒索我
She was unbalanced, she was blackmailing me.
我一周前跟她结束了
And I put an end to it a week ago.
她叫什么
What's her name?
什么…
Wha…?
- 她能跟这有什么关系… - 保罗
- What could she have to do with…? - Paul,
她叫什么
what is her name?
不
No.
No!
真是没想到
That's a curve ball.
嗯
Yeah.
每个手腕三道 垂直划
Three per wrist, vertical.
她可不是闹的
She wasn't fooling around.
嗯
Yeah.
看来她施的魔法很邪恶
Looks like she was working some heavyweight evil here.
嗯
Yup.
天啊
God!
该死的女巫 真是的
Frigging witches. Seriously, man, come on.
看来我们知道那颗兔牙哪来的了
Guess we know where she got the rabbit's teeth from.
保罗真是会挑人呢
Well, Paul sure knows how to pick them.
简直像《致命诱惑》重演
It's like Fatal Attraction all over again.
嗯
Yeah.
而且怎么每次都有兔子被害惨
And why does a rabbit always gets screwed on the deal?
小可怜
Poor little guy.
你知道我哪里不明白吗 迪恩
You know what I don't get, Dean?
如果她一心要复仇 为什么自杀
If she was so bent on revenge, why do this?
嗯
Well…
她杀了珍妮特·达顿 以为保罗也被她干掉了
she got Janet Dutton, thought she'd finished off Paul.
便决定自杀 算是被弃情人的帽子戏法了
Decided to cap herself, make it a spurned lover's hat trick.
或许吧
Maybe.
这看上去不像
I mean, this doesn't exactly look like a.
一个阳光稳定的人的客厅
TV room of a bright and stable person, you know.
是啊
No.
但是
But then…
还有这个
there's this.
又是巫术袋 搞什么
Another hex bag? Come on.
看来是刺杀啊
Looks like we got a hit?
女巫黑吃黑吗
Little witch-on-witch violence?
可能吧
I guess.
我发现了一具尸体 梅菲尔区309号
I'd like to report a dead body. 309 Mayfair Circle.
我的名字吗 嗯 我叫…
My name? Yeah, sure. My name is…
女巫为什么要相互残杀
Why are witches ganking each other?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我们可能遇到了女巫团
But I think maybe we got a coven on our hands.
好了
All right, all right.
我这就走
I'm going.
我可没被你们的读书俱乐部蒙蔽
I'm not fooled by your little book club, by the way.
我知道你们这些女人等我走后都做什么
I know what you ladies get up to when I'm gone.
就是扯闲篇
It's all dish and gossip.
罗恩
Ron.
你好 伊丽莎白
Hello, Elizabeth.
你们上次有人带书来是什么时候了
I mean, when's the last time anyone actually brought a book?
- 晚安 罗恩 - 晚安 罗恩
- Good night, Ron. - Good night, Ron.
好吧
All right.
他还不知道吗
He doesn't know?
你没告诉他吗
You didn't tell him?
阿曼达的事吗
About Amanda?
我觉得那是读书俱乐部的事 不是吗
I think that's book-club business, don't you?
谢谢 塔米
Thank you, Tammi.
警方刚抬走她的尸体
The police just took away her body.
怎么 我们就假装那事没发生吗
And what? We're just gonna pretend it didn't happen?
我们爱阿曼达的
We loved Amanda.
是真的
It's true.
但我们知道她有点不稳定
But we know that she was a little, well, unstable.
- 这也是真的 - 而且我们得承认
- Also true. - And we have to face it…
八成是她杀了珍妮特·达顿
she probably killed Janet Dutton.
人不会突然就把牙吐出来
People just don't spit out their teeth all of a sudden.
我们得停下了
We have to stop.
我们得中止读书俱乐部 这太过分了
We have to stop book club. This has all gone too far.
伊丽莎白 深呼吸
Elizabeth, just take a deep breath.
冷静下来
Calm down.
我们不能停下
We can't stop.
但都死人了
But people are dying.
阿曼达自杀了 是的
Amanda killed herself, yes…
是的 她还杀了珍妮特
and, yes, she killed Janet.
太可怕了 没错
Awful, awful business, of course.
但那都结束了
But that's all over now.
想想读书俱乐部为我们带来了什么好处
And think about what book club has gotten us?
你丈夫的升职
Your husband's promotion.
你赢得的夏威夷之旅
That little trip to Hawaii that you won.
还有我呢
And what about me?
我的自制陶器生意总算有起色了
My home pottery business is finally taking off.
你却想停下吗
And you wanna just stop?
你想停下吗
Do you wanna stop?
好了
Okay, now, come on.
我们时间不多
We don't have much time.
罗恩去打梦幻橄榄球了 一小时后就回来
Ron gets back from his fantasy football in an hour.
《暗影之书》 我们跪在你面前
Book of Shadows, we kneel before you.
让我们侍奉你的主人 你也服务我们
Let us serve your master as you serve us.
《暗影之书》 我们跪在你面前
Book of Shadows, we kneel before you.
让我们侍奉你的主人
Let us serve your master…
你肯定很擅长园艺
You must have a green thumb.
什么
Excuse me?
能让这些草药反季生长
Getting these herbs to grow out of season like this.
真是了不起
It's quite impressive.
抱歉 我该先自我介绍的
I'm sorry. I should have introduced myself first.
我是 巴克曼警探
I'm, uh, Detective Bachman.
这是特纳警探
This is Detective Turner.
我们在跟进阿曼达·伯恩斯的死
We're following up on Amanda Burns' death.
在街区里到处转转
Going around the neighborhood.
找邻居们聊聊什么的
talking to her neighbors and stuff like that.
但她不是…
But didn't she…?
她是自杀的 是吧
I mean, she killed herself, right?
或许吧
Maybe. Maybe.
我们听说你跟死者是朋友 是吗
We heard you were friends with the deceased. Is that right?
大概是吧
Yeah, I guess so.
你知道她施法的事吗
Do you have any idea about her practices?
抱歉 什么意思
I'm sorry. What kinda practices?
她家里有各种撒旦崇拜的器具
Well, see, her house was littered with satanic paraphernalia.
简直是黑色安息日
A regular black Sabbath.
不 那…
No. That…
她可是新教圣公会的
But she was an Episcopalian.
那她肯定是用错了《圣经》
Well, then we're pretty sure she was using the wrong Bible.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我很好
I'm fine.
蕾妮 这两位是警探
Renee, these are detectives.
他们说阿曼达…
They say Amanda was…
- 她在施法… - 抱歉 警探
- She was practicing… - Sorry, detectives.
你们能看得出 伊丽莎白有些难过
You can tell that Elizabeth is a little upset.
当然了 这位是…
Of course, Miss…?
蕾妮·范·艾伦太太
Mrs. Renee Van Allen.
要我给你拼出来吗
Would you like me to spell it for you?
我能行 谢谢
I'll get by, thanks.
阿曼达的事 让丽莎很难过
This Amanda business has been hard for Liz,
我们都很难过
for all of us.
是啊 你自以为了解一个人
Yeah, I mean, you think you know a person…
看来我们都有秘密 是吧
Well, I guess we all have secrets, don't we?
谢谢了
Well, thanks.
我们再联系
We'll be in touch.
祝你们愉快
Have a nice day.
再见
Bye.
那个伊丽莎白绝对是
Well, I'm already sold on that Elizabeth chick.
看到她的胜利花园了吗
You see that victory garden of hers?
颠茄 附子草 曼德拉草
Belladonna, wolf's bane, mandrake.
更别提我们提到法术时
Not to mention that flinch she threw.
她躲闪的样子
when we mentioned the occult.
她近来绝对是顺风顺水
Well, she's definitely had a good run lately.
纳税等级提升了不少 赢了太多彩票
Gone up a few tax brackets, won almost too many raffles.
就是那种黑魔法能换来的东西
The kind of thing a little black magic always helps with.
嗯
Yeah.
而且我觉得不止她一个
I don't think she's alone either.
看来蕾妮·范·艾伦太太
Looks like Mrs. Renee Van Allen.
这三个月来赢了几乎所有
has won almost every craft contest.
她参加的手工艺品大赛
she's entered in the past three months.
家政女王吗 除了魔鬼崇拜的部分
A regular Martha Stewart, huh? Except for the devil worship.
我觉得我们刚刚见到的就是女巫团
I'm thinking that was the coven we met back there,
只是少了个人
minus one member.
阿曼达显然是出了安全区
Amanda was clearly going off the reservation.
怎么 她们为保持表象而杀了她吗
What do you think, they killed her to keep up appearances?
她们看上去像群很看重表象的人 不是吗
Seems like an appearance kind of crowd. Don't you think?
嗯
Yeah.
如果她们杀了个疯子 我们该感谢她们吗
If they killed a nutjob, should we, uh, thank them or what?
她们也在施黑魔法 迪恩 得阻止她们
They're working black magic too, Dean. They need to be stopped.
「阻止」她们吗
Stopped like "stopped"?
她们是人 萨姆
They're humans, Sam.
她们是杀人犯
They're murderers.
烧死吧 女巫
Burn, witch, burn.
怎么回事
The hell?
露比
Ruby?
萨姆 听我说 没时间了
Sam, listen to me, there's no time.
什么 你说什么呢
What? What are you talking about?
你得马上离开
You've to get out of town.
这就是露比吗
So this is Ruby, huh?
- 未曾有幸呢 - 迪恩
- Never had the pleasure. - Dean.
我就希望你会再出现
I was hoping you'd show up again.
把那玩意对着别处
Point that thing somewhere else.
想得美
Right.
萨姆 拜托
Sam, please.
快走
Go.
上车离开 别回头
Get in the car. And don't look back.
为什么 我不懂
Why? I don't understand.
牛人
Hot stuff.
我们收拾得了几个小女巫 谢谢了
We can take care of a few kitchen witches. Thanks.
我才不是说那几个女巫 蠢蛋
I'm not talking about witches, you jackass.
女巫只是婊子
Witches are whores.
我是指她们侍奉的人
I'm talking about who they serve.
恶魔
Demons.
- 她们的法力来自恶魔 - 对
- They get their power from demons. - Yeah.
这里现在就有一个
And there's one here. Now.
怎么 除了你吗
What, you mean besides you?
萨姆 它知道你在这里
Sam, it knows you're in town.
它会来追杀你的
And it's gonna come after you.
你绝对应付不来
And it's way more than you can handle.
得了 这算什么
Come on. What is this, huh?
拜托告诉我你不会真听信她的吧
Please tell me you're not listening to this crap.
管好你哥哥 萨姆 如果你想保住他的命
Put a leash on your brother, Sam, if you wanna keep him.
迪恩 冷静下来
Dean, look, just chill out.
不
No. No.
她在扰乱你的心绪
She's messing with your head.
天知道为什么 他们就是这样的
God knows why. That's who they are.
我在说实话
I'm telling you the truth.
我还叫你闭嘴呢 贱人
And I'm telling you to shut up, bitch.
不好意思 你凭什么掺和这段对话
I'm sorry, why are you even a part of this conversation?
我不知道 或许因为他是我弟弟
I don't know. Maybe because he's my brother,
你个黑眼骚货
you black-eyed skank.
是啊 你那么在乎你弟弟
Right. Right. You care about your brother so much.
所以你几个月后要离开
That's why you're checking out in a few month,
丢下他一人
leaving him all alone?
- 闭嘴 - 至少让我努力救他
- Shut up. - At least let me try and save him,
因为你今后不能再这么做了
since you won't be here to do it anymore.
- 我叫你闭嘴 - 迪恩 别
- I said, shut up! - Dean, no!
你怎么想的
What the hell were you thinking?
什么
What?
我怎么想的
What the hell was I thinking?
她是个恶魔 萨姆 就这么简单 好吗
She's a demon, Sam. Period. All right?
他们想要我们死 我们想要他们死
They want us dead, we want them dead.
真有意思 我还记得俄亥俄州的那个恶魔女
That's funny, I remember that demon chick in Ohio.
凯茜吗
Casey?
你就不希望我杀她
You didn't want her dead.
是啊 她可没像钓鱼一样钓着我
Yeah. Well, she wasn't stringing me along like a fish on a hook.
没有人在钓着我
No one's stringing me along.
我知道这是危险的 她是危险的
Look, I know it's dangerous, that she is dangerous.
但不管怎样 她对我们有用
But like it or not, she's useful.
不 我们要在她杀了我们前杀了她
No. We kill her before she kills us.
拿什么杀她
Kill her with what?
她帮我们修好的枪吗
The gun she fixed for us?
能成功就行
Whatever works.
迪恩 如果她希望我们死
Dean, if she wants us dead,
她只需要不再救我们
all she has to do is stop saving our lives.
我们得开始看到大局 迪恩
Look, we have to start looking at the big picture, Dean.
开始考虑策略 提前做打算
Start thinking in strategies and moves ahead.
没那么简单了 我们不仅仅是在猎魔了
It's not so simple. We're not just hunting anymore.
我们在打仗
We're at war.
你感觉还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
你为什么总问我这个
Why are you always asking me that?
因为首先 你在听一个恶魔的建议
Because you're taking advice from a demon, for starters.
而且 你似乎
And by the way, you seem.
越来越不在意杀人了
less and less worried about offing people.
以前你很为此不安
You know, it used to eat you up inside.
那对我又有什么好处吗
Yeah. And what has that gotten me?
没有 但你就该是那样的 好吗
Nothing. But it's just what you're supposed to do. Okay?
我们该开着车
We're supposed to drive in the frigging car.
为这种事吵架
and frigging argue about this stuff, you know.
你念叨着什么生命可贵什么的
You go on about the sanctity of life and all that crap.
等等 你在气我开始认同你了吗
Wait. So you're mad because I'm starting to agree with you?
不 我没生气
No, I'm not mad. I'm…
我是担心 萨姆
I'm worried, Sam,
我担心你 因为你不像自己了
I'm worried, because you're not acting like yourself.
是啊 我是不像了
Yeah. You're right. I'm not.
我没办法
I don't have a choice.
那什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
迪恩 你要走了 是吧
Look, Dean, you're leaving, right?
我还得留在这个破烂的世界里
And I gotta stay here in this craphole of a world.
独自一人
Alone.
所以依我看
So the way I see it…
如果我想活下来 如果我想
if I'm gonna make it, if I'm gonna.
在你走后打好这场仗
fight this war after you're gone…
那我得改变
then I gotta change.
改变成什么
Change into what?
变成你
Into you.
我得更像你
I gotta be more like you.
你是怎么了
What's going on with you?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 萨姆 不对劲 - 怎么了
- Sam, something's wrong. - What?
我身体里像有一堆刀
Bunch of knives inside of me.
迪恩
Dean?
该死
Son of a bitch.
迪恩
Dean.
是女巫团 肯定是她们
The coven, man. It's gotta be the coven.
好 别急
Okay, don't worry.
迪恩 我找不到
Dean, I can't find it.
不
No.
萨姆 你干什么
Sam, what are you doing?
萨姆
Sam.
Sam!
天啊
My God!
放了他
Let him go.
放了谁 你干什么呢
Let who go? What are you doing?
你疯了 出去
You're insane. Get out.
听着 如果你知道我
Look, if you know about me…
就知道这把枪的威力
then you know about this gun.
你要害死我哥哥了
You're killing my brother.
放了他 远离祭坛
Now, let him go. Get away from the altar.
- 什么 - 马上
- What? - Now!
好吧
Okay.
你想杀我吗
You wanna kill me?
排队吧 贱人
Get in line, bitch.
别再喊我贱人了
Stop calling me bitch.
过去
Go.
怎么了 我们没伤害谁
What? We weren't hurting anyone.
拜托 我们都不认识你哥哥
Please. We don't even know your brother.
中止咒语 否则受死
Stop the spell. Or die.
- 五秒 - 什么
- Five seconds. - What?
- 四秒 - 不 别
- Four. - No, please.
别杀我们
Please don't kill us.
我们只是在帮蕾妮降低按揭利率
We were just getting Renee a lower mortgage rate.
下次你再拿那把枪指着我
Next time you point that gun at me,
我就不会只是消失那么简单了 明白吗
I'm not gonna just disappear. Understand?
你救了我
You saved my life.
别客气
Don't mention it.
那是什么东西
What was that stuff?
天啊 好恶心
God, it was ass.
味道像屎
It tasted like ass.
那叫巫术 蠢蛋
It's called witchcraft, short bus.
你才蠢蛋呢 蠢蛋
You're the short bus, short bus.
好吧 或许不是你
Okay. Maybe it's not you.
也不是你
Or you.
或许是你
Maybe it's you.
我不知道他在说什么
I don't even know what he's talking about.
你在说什么啊
What are you even talking about?
你们所有人 你们女巫团的所有人
I mean, all of you, everyone in your little coven,
都遇上了好运
you've all had runs of good fortune.
能上报的好运
Newsworthy good fortune.
除了你 塔米
Except for you, Tammi.
告诉我 为什么
Now tell me, why is that?
你自己不想要点什么吗
You didn't want anything for yourself?
还是因为你已经得到了你想要的
Or is it because you're already getting what you wanted?
比如她们的灵魂
Like these women's souls.
我不…我没…我说了
I can't. I'm not… I told you.
还挺聪明 大侦探
Nice dick work, Magnum.
放了
Let.
我
my brother.
哥哥
go.
怎么了 找不到我的巫术袋吗
What's wrong? Couldn't find my hex bag?
抱歉 亲爱的
Sorry, sweetheart…
但你哥哥的肺这会儿应该都咳在地上了
but your brother's lungs should be in the floor by now.
你麻烦大了 萨姆
You're in a lot of trouble, Sam.
塔米 你的眼睛怎么了
Tammi, what's wrong with your eyes?
塔米 你在干什么
Tammi, what are you doing?
蕾妮 闭上你的嘴
Renee, shut your painted hole.
什么
What?
我…
I will…
你不能…
You can't…
别想在我家耍威风 塔米·班顿
Not in my house, Tammi Benton.
听着 你抓到我了
Look, you got me.
放了那姑娘
Let the girl go.
别急 小伙子
Wait your turn, young man.
天啊
My God.
丽莎
Lizzie.
没事的
It's okay.
你不是塔米
You're not Tammi.
对 但我在用她的肉身
No, but I'm wearing her meat.
我总得想办法跟你们套近乎
I had to break the ice with you girls somehow.
你杀了蕾妮
You killed Renee.
蕾妮 阿曼达
Renee, Amanda.
被淘汰的女巫就是这下场
That's what happens to witches who get voted off the island.
你是谁
Who are you?
这说来有趣
Funny story, actually.
记得那些你向他们祈祷的黑暗恶魔力量吗
Remember all those dark, demonic forces you prayed to…
你发誓侍奉的力量
when you swore your servitude?
你以为你在向谁祈祷
Just who did you think you were praying to?
这不…
This… This isn't…
不可能
It can't be.
你以为是什么
What did you think it was?
假的吗
Make-believe?
积极思维吗
Positive thinking?
《秘密》吗
The Secret?
不是
No.
是我
It was me.
你把自己卖给了我 蠢猪
You sold yourself to me, you pig.
我只需要带一本好书来读书俱乐部
All I had to do was bring one good book to book club…
你们几个女人就排着队拍我马屁
and you ladies lined up to kiss my ass.
不
No. No.
我们不知道
We didn't know.
你知道 你一直都知道
Yes, you did. You knew every step of the way…
现在你的永恒灵魂属于我了
and now your ever-living souls are mine.
有评论吗 有问题吗
Comments? Questions?
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sammy Winchester.
来到了我们的小镇
Right here in our little town.
知道吗
You know,
我和我的朋友们在找你呢
my friends and I, we've been looking for you.
为什么
Why?
对了 因为我要带领什么破恶魔大军
Right, because I'm supposed to lead some piss-poor demon army.
不 完全不是
No, not at all.
你不是我们的弥赛亚
You're not our messiah.
我们不相信你
We don't believe in you.
但是西方崛起了新领袖
But there's a new leader rising in the West.
真正的领袖
A real leader.
那才是该压的马 萨姆
That's the horse to bet on, Sam.
那才是会撕碎这世界的人
The one who's gonna tear this world apart.
问题是 这个恶魔
Thing is, this demon…
他不怎么喜欢你
he doesn't like you very much.
不喜欢有竞争
Doesn't want the competition.
不是针对你
Nothing personal.
只是为了公关
It's a PR thing.
再见了
So bye-bye.
买一送一 不错
Two for one. Lovely.
等等
Wait.
别
Please.
我
I just…
就想谈谈
came to talk.
你冲出了魔鬼之门
You made it out of the Gate.
厉害
Impressive.
那真是场大战 是吧
It was a bitch of a fight, wasn't it?
地狱之门可不会开多久
Doors out of hell only open for so long.
你想要什么 露比
What do you want, Ruby?
没有你我好迷失
I've been lost without you.
重新收留我吧
Take me back.
所以我才把温家兄弟引了过来
That's why I led the Winchesters here.
- 我说了吧 - 他们是献给你的
- I told you so. - They're for you.
一份礼物
As a gift.
是吗
Really?
让我重新侍奉你吧
Let me serve you again.
我一直想这么做
I've wanted it.
我一直想要你
I've wanted you…
想要好久了
for so long.
你曾是我的骄傲
You were one of my best.
但话说回来 你一直是个撒谎婊子
But then again, you always were a lying whore.
你真要告诉我
You're really telling me.
你把注压在这俩谐星身上吗
you threw in your chips with Abbott and Costello here?
行了 起来
Come on. Get up.
我叫你起来
I said, get up.
这一刻似曾相识啊 是吧
We've been here before, haven't we?
她没告诉你们吗
She didn't tell you?
大概太丢脸了吧
Pretty mortifying, I guess.
她是我的
She was one of mine.
是我很久很久以前转化了她
I turned her out a long, long time ago.
露比 她曾是个女巫
Ruby, here, was a witch.
当然了 你那时还是人类
Of course that was when you were human.
不想你朋友知道吗
Didn't want your friends to know…
很多个世纪前 你把自己卖给了我
that all those centuries back you sold yourself to me?
不好意思吧
Embarrassing, I guess.
别担心 亲爱的
But don't worry, love.
你要去的地方没有秘密 记得吗
No secrets where you're heading, remember?
走吧
Go.
我会收拾这烂摊子
I'll clean up this mess.
来吧
Come on.
走
Go.
看来魔鬼可能真在乎
So the devil may care after all.
是要我相信这个吗
Is that what I'm supposed to believe?
我不相信魔鬼
I don't believe in the devil.
今晚真疯狂
Wacky night.
是这样吗
So let me get this straight.
你曾是人类
You were human once.
你死了 下了地狱 便成了…
You died, you went to hell, and became a…
对
Yeah.
多久以前
How long ago?
大瘟疫时代
Back when the plague was big.
所有人 每个可恶的恶魔
So all of them, every damn demon…
都曾是人类吗
they were all human once?
每个我见过的都是
Every one I've ever met.
看他们的样子可不像
Well, they sure don't act like it.
他们大部分已忘记了那是什么滋味
Most of them have forgotten what it means.
甚至忘了他们曾是人类
Or even that they were.
那就是下地狱后会发生的事 迪恩
That's what happens when you go to hell, Dean.
那就是地狱的本质
That's what hell is.
忘记你自己
Forgetting what you are.
恶魔给我上哲学课 免了吧 谢谢
A philosophy lesson from a demon. I'll pass, thanks.
不是哲学
It's not philosophy.
不是隐喻
It's not a metaphor.
深渊里是真有烈火
There's a real fire in the pit…
你无法想象的痛苦
Agonies you can't even imagine.
不 我看过《猛鬼追魂》 知道个大概
No, I saw Hellraiser. I get the gist.
其实 他们描述得还挺准确
Actually, they got that pretty close.
就除了各种定制皮具
Except for all the custom leather.
对了 答案是「是」
The answer is yes, by the way.
什么
Sorry?
是的
Yes,
你也会遭遇一样的事
the same thing will happen to you.
可能会要几个世纪
Might take centuries but…
但迟早 地狱会烧光你的人性
sooner or later, hell will burn away your humanity.
每个要下地狱的灵魂
Every hell-bound soul…
每一个都会变成别的东西
every one turns into something else.
变成我们
Turns you into us.
是的
So, yeah.
你跑不掉的
Yeah, you can count on it.
根本没办法让我不下地狱 是吧
There's no way of saving me from the pit, is there?
对
No.
那你为什么告诉萨姆有办法
Why did you tell Sam that you could?
为了让他跟我说话
So he would talk to me.
你们温家人很偏执
You Winchesters can be pretty bigoted.
我需要个借口 让他忘记…
I needed something to help him get past the whole…
你是恶魔吗
The demon thing?
这很难忘记
It's pretty hard to get past.
看看你
Look at you…
拼命装不在乎
trying to be all stoic.
天啊 真让人心碎
My God, it's heartbreaking.
你为什么告诉我这些
Why are you telling me all this?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
- 帮什么 - 萨姆
- Help with what? - With Sam.
你今晚捅死那恶魔的样子
The way you stuck that demon tonight…
很厉害
that was pretty tough.
萨姆快达到那水平了 但还差点
Sam's almost there but not quite.
你需要帮我为他做好准备
You need to help me get him ready…
迎接没有你的生活
for life without you…
独自扛起战争
to fight this war on his own.
露比
Ruby.
你为什么希望我们赢
Why do you want us to win?
还不明显吗
Isn't it obvious?
我跟他们不一样
I'm not like them.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why. I…
我也希望我跟他们一样 但我不一样
I wish I was, but I'm not.
我记得那是什么感觉
I remember what it's like.
你指什么
What what's like?
做人的感觉
Being human.